## **Doumi Athmane**

doumiathmane0@gmail.com

+213794038264

Algerie, Tipaza

I'm a software engineering, full stack developer passionate about new technologies. I have worked on many web applications from the design part to the deployment going through all development process using different technologies and tools.

## **Professional Experiences:**

→ Backend developer ( Jan 2023 - present) :

Company: Maystro Delivery

Designing, implementing and deploy new features

for

local business

Used technologies: Yii framework - Django Rest

Framework

GCP - Postgres

→ Full-stack developer (Oct 2021 - Dec 2022) :

Company: Easy Relay

Responsible for the entire development and

integration

### **Education:**

Computer science engineer : (2017 - 2022)
 speciality Software engineering

From : Higher school of computer science

ESI Algiers)

Master in computer science (2017 - 2022)

From: Higher school of computer science

ESI Algiers)

#### Skills:

• Backend: - Programming languages: PHP - NodeJS - Python - Java

- Frameworks : Yii framework - Laravel - Django & Django Rest Framework

- API development : RestAPI - GraphQL

• Frontend: - Programming languages: HTML - CSS - JS

- Frameworks : ReactJS - Bootstrap

Mobile : Kotlin

Databases: - SQL: MySQL - Postgres

- NoSQL: MongoDB

• Developpement tools: Version control (Github) - Docker - GCP - Jenkins for CI/CD - tests

(JUnit - Selenium - Jest)

Soft skills: Problem solving - Collaboration (Agile methodology - Trello - ClickUp)

# Projects:

<b>MyHealth (9 months):</b> a platform for monitoring patients with chronic illnesses by collecting their vital data, processing them and ultimately proceeding in the event of an emergency. Used technologies: NodeJS -Express - Sequelize - KotlinNET tizen - Angular
<b>School management (3 months)</b> : a web application to manage private schools, it contain different actors (Students - Administrators - Teachers and Parents) Used technologies: PHP (MVC) - HTML - CSS - Bootstrap - MySQL
<b>Medical-Consult (1 month)</b> : a mobile application for patients, it allows them to make appointments with their doctors and consult their treatments.  Used technologies: Kotlin - NodeJS - Express
<b>Menu Generator (1 month)</b> : a web application for restaurants, for managing and generating their menus based on the available ingredients.  Used technologies: Node IS - Express - React IS

## Find me:



https://www.linkedin.com/in/athmane-doumi-a0875816b/



https://github.com/Doumi-Athmane



https://www.linkedin.com/in/athmane-doumi-a0875816b/